A Guide to the Lucille P. Markey Charitable Trust records FA017
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Institutional Grants and Proposals, 1983-1998; 2
  - University of Wisconsin, Madison - Denied Proposals 85-77, 85-170, 85-182, 85-59, 86-139, 86-163, 88-11, 89-31, 90-44, 91-40, 91-6, 92-9, 93-28 (Reel 119, Frame 952)
  - University of Wisconsin, Madison - Grant 84-16 (Reel 120, Frame 1)
  - University of Wisconsin, Milwaukee - Denied Proposal 89-16 (Reel 120, Frame 646)
  - Wistar Institute - Denied Proposal 85-240 (Reel 120, Frame 672)
  - Worcester Foundation for Experimental Biology - Denied Proposal 87-52 (Reel 120, Frame 699)
  - Wright State University - Denied Proposal 86-77 (Reel 120, Frame 712)
  - Yale University - Denied Proposals 84-17, 91-27 (Reel 120, Frame 726)
  - Yale University - Grant 84-18 (Reel 120, Frame 784)
  - Yale University - Grant 88-16 (Reel 120, Frame 1070)
  - Yale University - Grant 93-11 (Reel 120, Frame 1088)
  - Yale University - Grant 96-11 (Reel 120, Frame 1278)
- Governance, 1981-1998; 3
  Series 3 is arranged in 4 subseries:
  Subseries 1 - Minutes
  Subseries 2 - Chairman, Board of Trustees
  Subseries 3 - Director of Medical Science
  Subseries 4 - Annual Reports
  The records of the governing committees and Trust administration document policy decisions, financial accountability, program direction, and managerial aspects of Trust maintenance. Some Committees existed during a portion of the Trust's operation, and others were combined and reformed to accommodate the variation in the number of participating individuals.
  - Minutes, 1983-1998; 1
    This subseries is arranged in five sections:
    Section A - Co-Personal Representatives and the Investment Committee
    Section B - Executive Committee
    Section C - Finance Committee
    Section D - Trustees Committee and Combined Trustees and Finance Committee
    Section E - Combined Trustees, Finance Committee and Executive Committee
    Each section is arranged chronologically by meeting date.
    The minutes found in this subseries document the Committee meetings held throughout the duration of the Trust's fifteen years of operation. These meetings were held in different locations in the United States. Numerous organizational meetings were held at the Trust's corporate headquarters in Miami, Florida in addition to meetings held in New York City; Chicago, Illinois; Menlo Park and Los Angeles, California; Denver and Colorado Springs, Colorado; Dallas, Texas; and Lexington, Kentucky, the site of Calumet Farms.
    Only the Trustees and Executive Committees existed during the full fifteen-year operation of the Markey Trust.
    - Co-Personal Representatives and the Investment Committee, 1983-1984; A
      This section is arranged chronologically by meeting date.
      - Co-Personal Representatives and the Investment Committee - 3 November 1983 - New York, New York, November 3, 1983 (Reel 121, Frame 1)
      - Meeting - 21 November 1983 - Miami, Florida, November 21, 1983 (Reel 121, Frame 5)
      - Investment Comittee - 6 December 1983 - Miami, Florida, December 6, 1983 (Reel 121, Frame 11)
      - Co-Personal Representatives and the Investment Committee - 10 May 1984 - New York, New York, May 10, 1984 (Reel 121, Frame 15)
      - Co-Personal Representatives and the Investment Committee - 10 July 1984 - Miami, Florida, July 10, 1984 (Reel 121, Frame 25)
      - Co-Personal Representatives and the Investment Committee - 7 August 1984 - New York, New York, August 7, 1984 (Reel 121, Frame 52)
      - Co-Personal Representatives and the Investment Committee - 5 November 1984 - New York, New York, November 5, 1984 (Reel 121, Frame 56)
    - Executive Committee, 1984-1993; B
      - Meeting - 31 January-1February 1984 - New York, New York, January 31-February 1, 1984 (Reel 121, Frame 60)
      - Meeting - 9 May 1984 - New York, New York, May 9, 1984 (Reel 121, Frame 66)
      - Meeting - 11 July 1984 - Miami, Florida, July 11, 1984 (Reel 121, Frame 89)
      - Meeting - 8 August 1984 - Chicago, Illinois, August 8, 1984 (Reel 121, Frame 94)
      - Meeting - 8 October 1984 - Boston, Massachusetts, October 8, 1984 (Reel 121, Frame 98)
      - Meeting - 8 November 1984 - Chicago, Illinois, November 8, 1984 (Reel 121, Frame 102)
      - Meeting - 30 January 1985 - Dallas, Texas, January 30, 1985 (Reel 121, Frame 108)
      - Meeting - 22 February 1985 (by telephone), February 22, 1985 (Reel 121, Frame 129)
      - Meeting - 10-11, 13 March 1985 - Los Angeles, California, March 10-11 & 13, 1985 (Reel 121, Frame 149)
      - Meeting - 9 April 1985 - Miami, Florida, April 9, 1985 (Reel 121, Frame 155)
      - Meeting - 30-31 July 1985 - New York, New York, July 30-31, 1985 (Reel 121, Frame 162)
      - Meeting - 8-9 October 1985 - New York, New York, October 8-9, 1985 (Reel 121, Frame 226)
      - Meeting - 25 October 1985 (by telephone), October 25, 1985 (Reel 121, Frame 254)
      - Meeting - 13 November 1985 - Chicago, Illinois, November 13, 1985 (Reel 121, Frame 257)
      - Meeting - 27 January 1986 - Dallas, Texas, January 27, 1986 (Reel 121, Frame 283)
      - Meeting - 26 February 1986 - Miami, Florida, February 26, 1986 (Reel 121, Frame 366)
      - Meeting - 16 April 1986 - Washington, D.C., April 16, 1986 (Reel 121, Frame 381)
      - Meeting - 7 May 1986 - Denver, Colorado, May 7, 1986 (Reel 121, Frame 466)
      - Meeting - 5 June 1986 (by telephone), June 5, 1986 (Reel 121, Frame 476)
      - Meeting - 8 July 1986 - New York, New York, July 8, 1986 (Reel 121, Frame 483)
      - Meeting - 22 July 1986 (by telephone), July 22, 1986 (Reel 121, Frame 605)
      - Meeting - 6 August 1986 (by telephone), August 6, 1986 (Reel 121, Frame 609)
      - Meeting - 11 September 1986 - Glen Cove, New York, September 11, 1986 (Reel 121, Frame 620)
      - Meeting - 11 November 1986 - New York, New York, November 11, 1986 (Reel 121, Frame 659)
      - Meeting - 28 January 1987 - Dallas, Texas, January 28, 1987 (Reel 121, Frame 683)
      - Meeting - 26 February 1987 - Miami, Florida, February 26, 1987 (Reel 121, Frame 721)
      - Meeting - 18 May 1987 (by telephone), May 18, 1987 (Reel 121, Frame 817)
      - Meeting - 4 June 1987 - New York, New York, June 4, 1987 (Reel 121, Frame 853)
      - Meeting - 29 July 1987 - New York, New York, July 29, 1987 (Reel 121, Frame 908)
      - Meeting - 10 September 1987 - Lake Bluff, Illinois, September 10, 1987 (Reel 122, Frame 1)
      - Meeting - 2 November 1987 - New York, New York, November 2, 1987 (Reel 122, Frame 8)
      - Meeting - 27-28 January 1988 - Dallas-Fort Worth Airport, Texas, January 27-28, 1988 (Reel 122, Frame 92)
      - Meeting - 20 April 1988 - New York, New York, April 20, 1988 (Reel 122, Frame 109)
      - Meeting - 27 July 1988 - New York, New York, July 27, 1988 (Reel 122, Frame 173)
      - Meeting - 9 November 1988 - New York, New York, November 9, 1988 (Reel 122, Frame 319)
      - Meeting - 7 February 1989 - Dallas, Texas, February 7, 1989 (Reel 122, Frame 417)
      - Meeting - 20 April 1989 - New York, New York, April 20, 1989 (Reel 122, Frame 471)
      - Meeting - 2 November 1989 - Chicago, Illinois, November 2, 1989 (Reel 122, Frame 606)
      - Meeting - 24 January 1990 - Dallas, Texas, January 24, 1990 (Reel 122, Frame 736)
      - Meeting - 26 April 1990 - New York, New York, April 26, 1990 (Reel 122, Frame 899)
      - Meeting - 24 July 1990 - New York, New York, July 24, 1990 (Reel 122, Frame 992)
      - Meeting - 30 October 1990 - New York, New York, October 30, 1990 (Reel 123, Frame 1)
      - Meeting - 30 January 1991 - Dallas, Texas, January 30, 1991 (Reel 123, Frame 67)
      - Meeting - 2 May 1991 - New York, New York, May 2, 1991 (Reel 123, Frame 182)
      - Meeting - 31 July 1990 (by telephone), July 31, 1991 (Reel 123, Frame 265)
      - Meeting - 29 October 1991 - New York, New York, October 29, 1991 (Reel 123, Frame 272)
      - Meeting - 9 January 1992 (by telephone), January 9, 1992 (Reel 123, Frame 340)
      - Meeting - 21 April 1992 - New York, New York, April 21, 1992 (Reel 123, Frame 344)
      - Meeting - 21, 23 April 1993 (by telephone), April 19 & 23, 1993 (Reel 123, Frame 390)
      - Meeting - 17 November 1993 - New York, New York, November 17, 1993 (Reel 123, Frame 397)
    - Finance Committee, 1985-1998; C
      - Memorandum - 6 December 1985, December 6, 1985 (Reel 123, Frame 472)
      - Meeting - 9 January 1986 - New York, New York, January 9, 1986 (Reel 123, Frame 488)
      - Meeting - 26 February 1986 - Miami, Florida, February 26, 1986 (Reel 123, Frame 589)
      - Meeting - 29 April 1986 (by telephone), April 29, 1986 (Reel 123, Frame 650)
      - Meeting - 8 May 1986 - Denver, Colorado, May 8, 1986 (Reel 123, Frame 674)
      - Meeting - 9 July 1986 - New York, New York, July 9, 1986 (Reel 123, Frame 691)
      - Meeting - 12 September 1986 - Glen Cove, New York, September 12, 1986 (Reel 123, Frame 741)
      - Meeting - 11 November 1986 - New York, New York, November 11, 1986 (Reel 123, Frame 803)
      - Meeting - 20 January 1987 - New York, New York, January 20, 1987 (Reel 123, Frame 840)
      - Meeting - 26 February 1987 - Miami, Florida, February 26, 1987 (Reel 123, Frame 876)
      - Meeting - 6 April 1987 - New York, New York, April 6, 1987 (Reel 123, Frame 914)
      - Meeting - 30 April 1987 - New York, New York, April 30, 1987 (Reel 124, Frame 1)
      - Meeting - 4 June 1987 - New York, New York, June 4, 1987 (Reel 124, Frame 15)
      - Meeting - 10-11 September 1987 - Lake Bluff, Illinois, September 10-11, 1987 (Reel 124, Frame 127)
      - Meeting - 24 September 1987 - New York, New York, September 24, 1987 (Reel 124, Frame 206)
      - Meeting - 2 October 1987 (by telephone), October 2, 1987 (Reel 124, Frame 211)
      - Meeting - 2 November 1987 - New York, New York, November 2, 1987 (Reel 124, Frame 220)
      - Executive Session - 4 December 1987 - Menlo Park, California, December 4, 1987 (Reel 124, Frame 376)
      - Meeting - 6 January 1988 - New York, New York, January 6, 1988 (Reel 124, Frame 379)
      - Meeting - 19 February 1988 - Miami, Florida, February 19, 1988 (Reel 124, Frame 391)
      - Meeting - 21 April 1988 - New York, New York, April 21, 1988 (Reel 124, Frame 397)
      - Meeting - 19 May 1988 (by telephone), May 19, 1988 (Reel 124, Frame 466)
      - Meeting - 7 June 1988 - Lexington, Kentucky, June 7, 1988 (Reel 124, Frame 480)
      - Meeting - 27 July 1988 - New York, New York, July 27, 1988 (Reel 124, Frame 559)
      - Meeting - 9 September 1988 - Woodlands, Texas, September 9, 1988 (Reel 124, Frame 580)
      - Meeting - 9 November 1988 - New York, New York, November 9, 1988 (Reel 124, Frame 708)
      - Meeting - 23-24 February 1989 - Miami, Florida, February 23-24, 1989 (Reel 124, Frame 778)
      - Meeting - 21 April 1989 - New York, New York, April 21, 1989 (Reel 125, Frame 1)
      - Meeting - 16 May 1989, May 16, 1989 (Reel 125, Frame 168)
      - Meeting - 15-16 June 1989 - New York, New York, June 15-16, 1989 (Reel 125, Frame 173)
      - Meeting - 8 September 1989 - Colorado Springs, Colorado, September 8, 1989 (Reel 125, Frame 254)
      - Meeting - 17 October 1989 - New York, New York, October 17, 1989 (Reel 125, Frame 479)
      - Meeting - 29 November 1989 - St. Louis, Missouri, November 29, 1989 (Reel 125, Frame 538)
      - Meeting - 28 February-1 March 1990 - Miami, Florida, February 28-March 1, 1990 (Reel 125, Frame 657)
      - Meeting - 26 April 1990 - New York, New York, April 26, 1990 (Reel 125, Frame 673)
      - Meeting - 23-24 May 1990 - Chicago, Illinois, May 23-24, 1990 (Reel 125, Frame 776)
      - Meeting - 24 July 1990 - New York, New York, July 24, 1990 (Reel 125, Frame 838)
      - Meeting - 9 September 1990 - Minneapolis, Minnesota, September 9, 1990 (Reel 126, Frame 1)
      - Meeting - 30 October 1990 - New York, New York, October 30, 1990 (Reel 126, Frame 92)
      - Meeting - 3 December 1990 - Menlo Park, California, December 3, 1990 (Reel 126, Frame 264)
      - Meeting - 27-28 February 1991 - Miami, Florida, February 27-28, 1991 (Reel 126, Frame 377)
      - Meeting - 3 May 1991 - New York, New York, May 3, 1991 (Reel 126, Frame 522)
      - Meeting - 28 May 1991, May 28, 1991 (Reel 126, Frame 637)
      - Meeting - 8 June 1991 - Prouts Neck, Maine, June 8, 1991 (Reel 126, Frame 640)
      - Meeting - 31 July 1991, July 31, 1991 (Reel 126, Frame 743)
      - Meeting - 13 September 1991 - Stone Mountain, Georgia, September 13, 1991 (Reel 126, Frame 784)
      - Meeting - 29 October 1991 - New York, New York, October 29, 1991 (Reel 126, Frame 873)
      - Meeting - 9 December 1991 - La Jolla, California, December 9, 1991 (Reel 127, Frame 1)
      - Meeting - 20 February 1992 - Miami, Florida, February 20, 1992 (Reel 127, Frame 46)
      - Meeting - 21 April 1992 - New York, New York, April 21, 1992 (Reel 127, Frame 156)
      - Meeting - 4 May 1992 (by telephone), May 4, 1992 (Reel 127, Frame 252)
      - Meeting - 19 May 1992 - Chicago, Illinois, May 19, 1992 (Reel 127, Frame 255)
      - Meeting - 10 September 1992 - Denver, Colorado, September 10, 1992 (Reel 127, Frame 381)
      - Meeting - 30 October 1992 - New York, New York, October 30, 1992 (Reel 127, Frame 448)
      - Meeting - 8 December 1992 - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, December 8, 1992 (Reel 127, Frame 516)
      - Meeting - 4 March 1993 - Miami, Florida, March 4, 1993 (Reel 127, Frame 602)
      - Meeting - 22 April 1993 - New York, New York, April 22, 1993 (Reel 127, Frame 663)
      - Meeting - 25 May 1993 - Durham, North Carolina, May 25, 1993 (Reel 127, Frame 979)
      - Meeting - 9 September 1993 - Menlo Park, California, September 9, 1993 (Reel 128, Frame 1)
      - Meeting - 29 October 1993 - New York, New York, October 29, 1993 (Reel 128, Frame 80)
      - Meeting - 6 December 1993 - Baltimore, Maryland, December 6, 1993 (Reel 128, Frame 178)
      - Meeting - 11 March 1994 - Miami, Florida, March 11, 1994 (Reel 128, Frame 230)
      - Meeting - 9 May 1994 - New York, New York, May 9, 1994 (Reel 128, Frame 282)
      - Meeting - 7 June 1994 - Boston, Massachusetts, June 7, 1994 (Reel 128, Frame 377)
      - Meeting - 8 September 1994 - Atlanta, Georgia, September 8, 1994 (Reel 128, Frame 444)
      - Meeting - 5 December 1994 - Nashville, Tennessee, December 5, 1994 (Reel 128, Frame 512)
      - Meeting - 24 February 1995 - Tallahassee, Florida, February 24, 1995 (Reel 128, Frame 581)
      - Meeting - 8 May 1995 (by telephone), May 8, 1995 (Reel 128, Frame 636)
      - Meeting - 16 May 1995 - Seattle, Washington, May 16, 1995 (Reel 128, Frame 656)
      - Meeting - 31 May 1995 - New York, New York, May 31, 1995 (Reel 128, Frame 702)
      - Meeting - 14 September 1995 - Lincolnshire, Illinois, September 14, 1995 (Reel 128, Frame 725)
      - Meeting - 6 December 1995 - New York, New York, December 6, 1995 (Reel 128, Frame 802)
      - Meeting - 27 February 1996 - Miami, Florida, February 27, 1996 (Reel 128, Frame 851)
      - Meeting - 15 April 1996 (by telephone), April 15, 1996 (Reel 128, Frame 901)
      - Meeting - 7 May 1996 - Charlottesville, Virginia, May 7, 1996 (Reel 128, Frame 913)
      - Meeting - 13 August 1996 (by telephone), August 13, 1996 (Reel 129, Frame 1)
      - Meeting - 6 September 1996 - Lexington, Kentucky, September 6, 1996 (Reel 129, Frame 27)
      - Meeting - 3 December 1996 - Menlo Park, California, December 3, 1996 (Reel 129, Frame 69)
      - Meeting - 27 October 1997 (by telephone), October 27, 1997 (Reel 129, Frame 116)
      - Meeting - 10 December 1997 (by telephone), December 10, 1997 (Reel 129, Frame 171)
      - Meeting - 5 March 1998 (by telephone), March 5, 1998 (Reel 129, Frame 215)
    - Trustees Committee and Combined Trustees and Finance Committee, 1983-1998; D
      - Combined Trustees and Finance Committee - 28 October 1983 - Atlanta, Georgia, October 28, 1983 (Reel 129, Frame 263)
      - Combined Trustees and Finance Committee - 27-29 February 1984 - Miami, Florida, February 27-29, 1984 (Reel 129, Frame 337)
      - Combined Trustees and Finance Committee - 30-31 May 1984 - Chicago, Illinois, May 30-31, 1984 (Reel 129, Frame 494)
      - Combined Trustees and Finance Committee - 9-10 August 1984 - Chicago, Illinois, August 9-10, 1984 (Reel 129, Frame 640)
      - Combined Trustees and Finance Committee - 8-9 November 1984 - Chicago, Illinois, November 8-9, 1984 (Reel 129, Frame 742)
      - Combined Trustees and Finance Committee - 14 February 1985 - Miami, Florida, February 14, 1985 (Reel 129, Frame 824)
      - Combined Trustees and Finance Committee - 9-10 May 1985 - Lexington, Kentucky, May 9-10, 1985 (Reel 130, Frame 1)
      - Trustees Committee - 8-9 August 1985 - Menlo Park, California, August 8-9, 1985 (Reel 130, Frame 166)
      - Trustees Committee - 14 November 1985 - Chicago, Illinois, November 14, 1985 (Reel 130, Frame 255)
      - Trustees Committee - 27 February 1986 - Miami, Florida, February 27, 1986 (Reel 130, Frame 359)
      - Trustees Committee - 8 May 1986 - Denver, Colorado, May 8, 1986 (Reel 130, Frame 535)
      - Trustees Committee - 12 September 1986 - Glen Cove, New York, September 12, 1986 (Reel 130, Frame 681)
      - Trustees Committee - 12 November 1986 - New York, New York, November 12, 1986 (Reel 131, Frame 1)
      - Trustees Committee - 4 June 1987 - New York, New York, June 4, 1987 (Reel 131, Frame 158)
      - Trustees Committee - 11 September 1987 - Lake Bluff, Illinois, September 11, 1987 (Reel 131, Frame 359)
      - Trustees Committee - 3 December 1987 - Menlo Park, California, December 3, 1987 (Reel 131, Frame 530)
      - Trustees Committee - 19 February 1988 - Miami, Florida, February 19, 1988 (Reel 131, Frame 727)
      - Trustees Committee - 7 June 1988 - Lexington, Kentucky, June 7, 1988 (Reel 131, Frame 878)
      - Combined Trustees and Finance Committee - 9 September 1988 - Woodlands, Texas, September 9, 1988 (Reel 132, Frame 1)
      - Trustees Committee - 8 December 1988 - Menlo Park, California, December 8, 1988 (Reel 132, Frame 158)
      - Combined Trustees and Finance Committee - 23-24 February 1989 - Miami, Florida, February 23-24, 1989 (Reel 132, Frame 315)
      - Combined Trustees and Finance Committee - 15 June 1989 - New York, New York, June 15, 1989 (Reel 132, Frame 392)
      - Combined Trustees and Finance Committee - 8 September 1989 - Colorado Springs, Colorado, September 8, 1989 (Reel 132, Frame 514)
      - Trustees Committee - 29-30 November 1989 - St. Louis, Missouri, November 29-30, 1989 (Reel 132, Frame 747)
      - Combined Trustees and Finance Committee - 28 February-1 March 1990 - Miami, Florida, February 28-March 1, 1990 (Reel 133, Frame 1)
      - Combined Trustees and Finance Committee - 23-24 May 1990 - Chicago, Illinois, May 23-24, 1990 (Reel 133, Frame 117)
      - Combined Trustees and Finance Committee - 6 September 1990 - Minneapolis, Minnesota, September 6, 1990 (Reel 133, Frame 298)
      - Combined Trustees and Finance Committee - 3 December 1990 - Menlo Park, California, December 3, 1990 (Reel 133, Frame 480)
      - Combined Trustees and Finance Committee - 27 February 1991 - Miami, Florida, February 27, 1991 (Reel 133, Frame 664)
      - Combined Trustees and Finance Committee - 8 June 1991 - Prouts Neck, Maine, June 8, 1991 (Reel 133, Frame 823)
      - Trustees Committee - 13 September 1991 - Stone Mountain, Georgia, September 13, 1991 (Reel 133, Frame 954)
      - Combined Trustees and Finance Committee - 9 December 1991 - La Jolla, California, December 9, 1991 (Reel 134, Frame 1)
      - Combined Trustees and Finance Committee - 20 February 1992 - Miami, Florida, February 20, 1992 (Reel 134, Frame 193)
      - Trustees Committee - 19 May 1992 - Chicago, Illinois, May 19, 1992 (Reel 134, Frame 346)
      - Trustees Committee - 30 June 1992 - by Telephone, June 30, 1992 (Reel 134, Frame 547)
      - Trustees Committee - 12 August 1992 - by Telephone, August 12, 1992 (Reel 134, Frame 554)
      - Combined Trustees and Finance Committee - 10 September 1992 - Englewood, Colorado, September 10, 1992 (Reel 134, Frame 584)
      - Combined Trustees and Finance Committee - 8 December 1992 - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, December 8, 1992 (Reel 134, Frame 743)
      - Trustee Committee - 22 January 1993 - by Telephone, January 22, 1993 (Reel 134, Frame 900)
      - Combined Trustees and Finance Committee - 4 March 1993 - Miami, Florida, March 4, 1993 (Reel 134, Frame 915)
      - Combined Trustees and Finance Committee - 25 May 1993 - Durham, North Carolina, May 25, 1993 (Reel 135, Frame 1)
      - Combined Trustees and Finance Committee - 9 September 1993 - Menlo Park, California, September 9, 1993 (Reel 135, Frame 151)
      - Combined Trustees and Finance Committee - 6 December 1993 - Baltimore, Maryland, December 6, 1993 (Reel 135, Frame 279)
      - Combined Trustees and Finance Committee - 11 March 1994 - Miami, Florida, March 11, 1994 (Reel 135, Frame 446)
      - Combined Trustees and Finance Committee - 7 June 1994 - Boston, Massachusetts, June 7, 1994 (Reel 135, Frame 611)
      - Combined Trustees and Finance Committee - 8 September 1994 - Atlanta, Georgia, September 8, 1994 (Reel 135, Frame 797)
      - Trustees Committee - 5 July 1994, July 5, 1994 (Reel 135, Frame 994)
      - Combined Trustees and Finance Committee - 5 December 1994 - Nashville, Tennessee, December 5, 1994 (Reel 136, Frame 1)
      - Combined Trustees and Finance Committee - 24 February 1995 - Tallahassee, Florida, February 24, 1995 (Reel 136, Frame 145)
      - Combined Trustees and Finance Committee - 16 May 1995 - Seattle, Washington, May 16, 1995 (Reel 136, Frame 236)
      - Combined Trustees and Finance Committee - 14 September 1995 - Lincolnshire, Illinois, September 14, 1995 (Reel 136, Frame 308)
      - Combined Trustees and Finance Committee - 6 December 1995 - New York, New York, December 6, 1995 (Reel 136, Frame 429)
      - Combined Trustees and Finance Committee - 27 February 1996 - Miami, Florida, February 27, 1996 (Reel 136, Frame 506)
      - Combined Trustees and Finance Committee - 7 May 1996 - Charlottesville, Virginia, May 7, 1996 (Reel 136, Frame 620)
      - Combined Trustees and Finance Committee - 6 September 1996 - Lexington, Kentucky, September 6, 1996 (Reel 136, Frame 722)
      - Combined Trustees and Finance Committee - 4 December 1996 - Menlo Park, California, December 4, 1996 (Reel 136, Frame 824)
      - Combined Trustees and Finance Committee - 25 February 1997 - Miami, Florida, February 25, 1997 (Reel 136, Frame 931)
      - Combined Trustees and Finance Committee - 13 May 1997 - North Tarrytown, New York, May 13, 1997 (Reel 137, Frame 1)
      - Combined Trustees and Finance Committee - 26 March 1998 - Lexington, Kentucky, March 26, 1998 (Reel 137, Frame 170)
    - Combined Trustees, Finance Committee and Executive Committee, 1987; E
      - Combined Trustees, Finance Committee and Executive Committee - 26-27 February 1987 - Lexington, Kentucky, February 26-27, 1987 (Reel 137, Frame 300)
  - Chairman, Board of Trustees, 1954-1997 1982-1997; 2
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically.
    This subseries includes correspondence, memoranda, and notes generated by Louis J. Hector, who served as the Chairman of the Board of the Markey Trust for the duration of the Trust's operation. Records include executive committee material, general correspondence, and trustee correspondence. Mr. Hector also maintained files pertaining to other Board members and special projects. Information pertaining to the origins and history of the Trust and the attempt to contract a written history is also documented. Trustees' and Officers' biographies are included in the series.
    - Dickason, John H., 1984-1986 (Reel 137, Frame 480)
    - Executive Committee, 1984-1993 (Reel 137, Frame 512)
    - Foundations - Miscellaneous, 1982-1985 (Reel 137, Frame 652)